<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Sidhant Nagpal</title>
 <link href="https://sidhantnagpal.github.io/" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://sidhantnagpal.github.io"/>
 <updated>2018-04-24T12:25:34+05:30</updated>
 <id>https://sidhantnagpal.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Sidhant Nagpal.</name>
   <email>sidhantnagpal97 [at] gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Selected for GSoC '18</title>
   <link href="https://sidhantnagpal.github.io/2018/04/gsoc-1.html"/>
   <updated>2018-04-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>https://sidhantnagpal.github.io/2018/04/gsoc-1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am extremely glad to inform that my &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/sidhantnagpal/gsoc/wiki/GSoC-2018-Application-Sidhant-Nagpal:-Transforms,-Convolution-&amp;amp;-Linear-Recurrence-Evaluation&quot;&gt;proposal&lt;/a&gt; ‘Transforms, Convolution &amp;amp; Linear Recurrence Evaluation’ has been accepted by SymPy for Google Summer of Code 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the unitiated, SymPy is a Computer Algebra System (CAS) written entirely in Python. SymPy has participated in every Google Summer of Code since 2007, before it was started as a project by Ondrej Certik (&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/certik&quot;&gt;certik&lt;/a&gt;) in 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My official mentors are Aaron Meurer (&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/asmeurer&quot;&gt;asmeurer&lt;/a&gt;) and Kalevi Suominen (&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jksuom&quot;&gt;jksuom&lt;/a&gt;).  Aaron Meurer (who also joined from GSoC) is the lead developer of SymPy since 2011. Kalevi Suominen (SymPy Member) has mentored for Google Summer of Code in 2016 and 2017. I am extremely lucky to have gotten an opportunity to work with such experienced developers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the Community Bonding Period, I will complete the following tasks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Setting up the blog with RSS feed for GSoC posts (for &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.sympy.org&quot;&gt;planet.sympy.org&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discussing the possible modes of communication, and getting information for timings and weekly meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Resolving any other issues that might arise during the Coding Period.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Getting the details for expected work to be done, discussing the API of the modules to be implemented and studying the existing modules which might be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to thank the SymPy team, especially my mentors - Aaron Meurer and Kalevi Suominen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to a great summer.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>First Post</title>
   <link href="https://sidhantnagpal.github.io/2018/04/first-post.html"/>
   <updated>2018-04-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated>
   <id>https://sidhantnagpal.github.io/2018/04/first-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>